We're contacting the stores, the customers, the regulators,
and handling the distribution centre.
Now for more hard work.
We have three days to get control of this story.
Farms.
Packaging.
Northwest distribution centre.
And the stores.
This is what you're going to need to concentrate on: E. coli.
The northwest distribution centre is where it was found.
But that doesn't mean that's where the contamination occurred.
— Maybe, maybe not.
The stores we can eliminate —
because fortunately we got it before it got out there.
Thankfully.
So this is what we need to be looking at,
and we need to be thorough, meticulous —
consider all the possibilities.
I'll start with the packaging facility.
You have to look at where the meat is prepped, packaged, stored — everything.
— Absolutely.
Okay, I'll take the northwest distribution centre.
I'm very familiar with it.
And I'll take the family farms that supply CarneCarne with beef.
All five of them, right? — Yeah.
Make every effort. Pull out every stop. No stone unturned.
We'll go over it with a fine-tooth comb.
I'll cover everything on the suppliers' side.
And reach out if you need support.
Yes, no doubt.
My team is ready. — Okay. Anything else?
Okay, we'll reconvene on Friday.
The survival of CarneCarne may depend on this press conference.
So I've got some media to do and I'll be back and forth,
but don't feel like you need to wait on me for anything.
You have my full confidence.